icici lombard and cnbc tv 18 present
india risk management awards risk master
class
one basic mega trend there is a greater
awareness of health which has come
because of this covet and so the allied
product is a health insurance
which which has picked up in a very big
week
so companies have started taking larger
covers they have started taking pop-up
covers etc
the second biggest trend which is also
quite obvious is that the
cyber security has become because there
are boundaries organizations
uh organizations have got created most
of us are uh
either working from home or their uh we
are we are taking up we are working on
rooster bases sometimes we are working
from office sometimes we are working
from home
now the demand for uh cyber security
covers both in large companies as well
as in msme says increased multi-fold
and we are seeing increased demand for
cyber security covers and for data
breaches
another thing in order to uh continue
functioning the way uh we wanted to be
we see that uh unmanned aerial vehicles
like drones etc
are started being used so um this is
has emerged as a new area of insurance
so drone insurance has uh
is another new area of insurance which
has erupted in india
and although it is small as of today but
i see this in next to
three to five years becoming very big
icici lombard
and cnbc tv 18 present india risk
management awards
risk master class